Guide to the St. Thomas More Editorial Project, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- University Library. St. Thomas More Editorial Project, 1958-1994; Accession 1997-A-025
  - Kermode, Prof. J.F., 1958 (Box 11, Folder 137)
  - Kiernan, Michael T., 1963 (Box 11, Folder 138)
  - Kirby, Thomas A., 1960 (Box 11, Folder 139)
  - Knowles, David D., Last Letter, September 3, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 140)
  - Klein, Undated (Box 11, Folder 141)
  - Konecsni, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 142)
  - Korn, Bertram W., 1962 (Box 11, Folder 144)
  - Kossow, Richard, 1962-1964 (Box 11, Folder 145)
  - Lammers, Estelle (Sunday Visitor article), 1966 (Box 11, Folder 146)
  - Langan, Thomas, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 147)
  - Lanham, Richard, October 14, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 148)
  - Lang, Michael, March 30, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 149)
  - Larkin, J.F., C.S.V., March 16, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 150)
  - Larkman, Jane, O.W.P., 1969 (Box 11, Folder 151)
  - Lewis, C.S., August 30, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 152)
  - Lewis, Sylvia, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 153)
  - Lievsay, John L., April 5, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 154)
  - Lipking, Joanna, July 14, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 155)
  - Longmans, Green and Co. Ltd, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 156)
  - Lonsdale, Roger, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 157)
  - Loomie, Albert J., S.J., November 16, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 158)
  - Lordi, R.J., October 12, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 159)
  - Lynch, Charles Arthur; Brown University, 1958-1961 (Box 11, Folder 160)
  - Lynch, Edward J., 1965 (Box 11, Folder 161)
  - MacMillan, Gretchen, December 7, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 162)
  - Maguire, Rev. John, C.S.C., June 29, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 163)
  - Mahoney, John L., 1964-1970 (Box 11, Folder 164)
  - Major, John, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 165)
  - Malizia, Maria E., 1971 (Box 11, Folder 166)
  - Malmed, Richard, April 10, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 167)
  - Marc'hadour, 1959-1963 (Box 11, Folder 168)
  - Levine, Mortimer (part 1 and 2), June 1966-1969 (Box 11, Folder 169-170)
  - Levin, Richard; Storybrook, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 171)